[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
SHIPPING COST
Good morning.
- Hello, Mr. Gong. - Morning, Ms. Jang.
When did you get to work?
I got to the café an hour ago.
I came in an hour and ten minutes ago.
Why did you come so early?
What about you?
I asked you first.
I don't want to answer first.
That's why I asked you first.
I do this when I'm nervous.
I work harder
get things ready faster
try to sleep less
and even run simulations in my head.
It's your turn now.
I miscalculated the time.
I meant to get here a little early, but I came too early.
Aren't I pathetic, how I'm always tense and nervous?
Not at all.
I think that's why you're good at what you do.
You don't make mistakes.
Me? I make a ton of mistakes.
Do you?
Nothing ever goes the way I plan.
I make loads of mistakes.
But if you practice hard enough
you can make up for the mistakes.
Let's go. Time to make some mistakes.
EPISODE 7: NOTHING HAS CHANGED
SALES DIVISION 2 EXPORT SALES CONTRACT
Mr. Choi.
I asked for all documents produced or received by Sales Division 2
in the last two years, separated by team.
Is this everything?
It's all here, as you asked.
We will penalize you if we find anything missing.
I'm sure you will. I know that.
I hope that never happens.
AUDIT IN PROGRESS AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Do we have to go through all that?
- Hi, Ji-hye. - Enjoy your meal.
- Enjoy. - You too.
Do you think Mr. Gong and Ms. Jang ate lunch?
They'll eat something way nicer. Why would you worry?
Mr. Yang.
What will happen to Division 2?
All we have so far is a tip-off.
They might find nothing.
I don't know much about this
but I hope they don't find anything.
Do you think that's the best outcome?
Of course.
We're all family here. I hope no one has to suffer.
Why would no one suffer?
If they find nothing, Mr. Gong and Ms. Jang suffer.
Oh, is that how it works?
When it's about work, there's no such thing as nothing.
There must always be a result.
The only difference is whether it's a scratch or a grave injury.
Then we should hope they find something.
My personal wish is
that they find a small mistake that results in a scratch.
Best-case scenario, everyone gets off with a scratch.
Is there anything we could do to help?
In that case, Ji-hye...
Pray and hope the heavens help us.
So they return unscathed.
Okay.
I love that you cut up the pork cutlet.
Wait, you said you didn't want any.
Mr. Lee Jong-hyun.
You've done business with us for seven years.
Yes.
Considering the circumstances, I'll get to the point.
Sure. That would benefit everyone.
I checked the details of the contract you signed with us.
It says the margin is 70%.
Given the brand's recognition and influence overseas
it's a much better offer than usual.
Can you describe how the negotiations went?
Hang on.
Isn't the margin way too low?
It is. It's almost the same as what we get.
Division 1 imports foreign brands
and Division 2 exports domestic brands
and yet the margin is almost the same?
Domestic brands aren't that well-known overseas.
Shouldn't Division 2 get a bigger margin?
There could be a side agreement.
The contract says 70%, but in reality, they get 75%.
And someone pockets the 5% difference.
Our brand has weakened since
but we once hit 50 billion won in sales with a single brand.
Our brand awareness in Asia is improving.
I don't think we're taking too much.
Did you bring the contract?
I believe we asked you to.
Here you go.
He won't admit to it.
Their contract will say the same as ours.
There's no issue with the contract.
We can't find anything unless we check their accounts.
You won't get anything from the accounts, either.
They made it so business expenses don't require receipts.
They'd have paid in cash.
How about pressuring them by saying we'll file a complaint?
Mr. Lee.
We suspect you paid kickbacks under the table.
That's nonsense.
There were no kickbacks.
Admit to it now, and it'll be kept between us.
We can penalize our personnel, and you can handle yours.
However, if you don't admit to it
we have no choice but to involve prosecution.
Do you have any proof to warrant that?
Would a prosecutor investigate on suspicion only, without proof?
There's circumstantial evidence.
Some of our staff have a conscience, and they blew a whistle.
File a complaint and have them investigate.
But if they don't find anything
I will hold Hongsung responsible.
How?
How will you hold us responsible?
Do you think we're incapable of taking action?
Is that why you're saying you'll do something
when you can't really do anything?
You've gone a little too far.
Is this the price I pay for doing business with Hongsung?
You can't treat me like a common criminal.
They wouldn't have come this far if a warning worked at all.
True. They'd be well-prepared.
This is as far as an audit can go.
We can't check personal accounts or search another company's office.
I really hate it
but in this situation
the only thing we can do is give a warning.
"We know what you did, but we'll let you off this time."
That alone works sometimes.
Most people decide to play it safe.
We can't do that this time.
The VP ordered this audit, and the whole board is involved.
We must bring them something.
Then find me something.
All I know is the law, and it looks fine to me.
This is definitely odd.
My experience tells me to focus
on money going out rather than money coming in.
SHIPPING COST BRICLOGIX
Can I ask why Hongsung covered the shipping costs?
That depends on the agreement.
No.
Shipping costs are never covered by the brand controller.
That's included in the margin.
That might never happen elsewhere
but we agreed to it.
That's how considerate Mr. Choi is.
Ask him about it.
We already did.
That's the shipping company's bank statement.
It's a sole proprietorship, so it conducts transactions freely.
The owner already confessed
to receiving payments from both companies
laundering them as salaries, and returning the money to you.
This is what I think happened.
You kept getting off with warnings
and no one actually did anything.
So you got more brazen.
You and us both.
Will you admit to it now?
Jeez.
You should've said from the start that you knew everything.
Why did you make me lie?
We gave you a chance.
And you just lost it.
You should've said it was a fucking chance.
How much is the shipping cost?
It's 2% of the total invoiced amount.
You took it, but instead of keeping it all to yourself
you gave some of it to the brand?
I'm asking you.
I'm sorry, sir.
He got a kickback from a kickback.
He knew you were taking from the company
so he asked you for a piece of the pie.
What did they take us for, making a demand like that?
I'm sorry, sir.
What are you sorry about?
You wouldn't have done this if you felt bad.
Mr. Gong.
Yes, sir.
Apart from the shipping costs, you suspect a side agreement?
Yes, the brand margin was excessively high.
VICE PRESIDENT KOO IN-MOCK
Mr. Choi.
Yes, sir.
How about you admit to what you did
cough up as much of the money you can
and leave voluntarily?
Do you need time to think?
No, sir.
I'll cooperate with the Audit Team.
- Yoon. - Yes, sir.
Aren't you the youngest associate director?
Yes, I am.
You might also have the shortest tenure ever.
This is why
you should never be proud of an early promotion
or despair that things are taking too long for you.
This is what people are like.
Some rise fast only to fall fast.
I have nothing more to say about that.
Ms. Park.
Yes, sir.
Handle Division 2 as well for a while.
Any issues with that?
No, sir.
You can go ahead.
HOT MILK COFFEE 600 WON
Thank you.
I haven't been here in a while.
We used to sit out here often.
Our presence makes other employees uncomfortable.
Exactly.
Is it the title or the age?
Everyone complains about us.
What will you do next?
I don't know.
I'm too afraid to do my own thing
so I'd like to find a decent opening.
But I doubt anyone would want a troublemaker like me.
It's too late for regret.
Sorry about that.
I get it, though.
I think I might have done the same.
A uselessly lofty title means more expenses.
People are watching, so you have to be seen at decent places
but not places that are too fancy.
Others with our titles own a nice place and a nice car
yet you're still struggling to pay off a mortgage.
That's when you start to want more.
It doesn't help that others embezzle too.
It feels like staying honest means falling behind.
It starts off by accepting a kickback you're offered.
Then you end up stealing the shipping costs.
It doesn't take much to become lousy.
Even people like you, who were once so decent.
I have no excuses.
Don't say that.
I didn't bring you out here to lecture you.
No, I should've been...
I should've been lectured.
If I'd remained under you...
this wouldn't have happened.
Being a parent whose child committed a crime.
Do you know that feeling?
The child must pay for what they did.
But despite what they did
you still love your child.
You wonder if you failed them somehow.
- That's it. - I'm so sorry.
I just...
I just wanted to have
a coffee out here with you like the old times.
Tell me when you decide what to do.
And if you need help.
I will.
Thank you, Ms. Park.
Thank you.
- Mr. Gong. - Yes?
How did it go? I haven't heard anything.
The Audit Team will be wrapping it up.
Did you see the holiday gift?
But they left her out again...
Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Gong.
No, go ahead.
Did you check my proposal?
Yes, I did.
The son of the mall's VP is getting married this weekend?
Yes, we sent a flower arrangement in Hongsung's name.
Who paid for it?
We put it on your card.
You should've put it on the director's card.
She told us to put it on yours.
Darn it.
What is it this time?
There's something we must sort out before the holiday.
Let's do it now.
- What is this? - An idea Team 4 came up with.
Team 4?
How are things over there?
Mr. Oh is struggling with the workload without a superior.
Let's do it one at a time.
Don't you see the mess I'm in?
I'm figuring out Division 2 on top of my usual workload.
They want to work for a commission?
The profit is low, but so is the risk.
I thought it could be a decent long-term project.
- Mr. Oh brought this to you? - Yes.
Was it his idea?
I'm not sure about that.
Get him in here.
Come and sit next to him.
- Hello, sir. - Hi.
Did you come up with this on your own?
It was Mr. Jeong's idea, but I came up with all the details.
He said it would be a good first project.
I can tell how much you've put into your first project.
It's like my own baby.
Oh, dear...
Jeong was way worse than I thought.
A non-profit business isn't just for anyone.
First, we must survive until we turn a profit.
Even when the industry is booming
no one would rely on a single non-profit business.
See if they're doing business with Jeong's company.
I bet they signed the real business with a huge margin.
We do all the hard work while Jeong takes all the profit.
Do you get what I'm saying, Mr. Oh?
Yes.
You made a decent dish, but the ingredients were rotten.
Bring me something else.
I liked the details, so don't blame yourself.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
You can go. Gong, you stay.
Do you know how humiliating that is?
If we approve this after demolishing a whole division
they'll call us honest but incompetent.
Do you want them to say they'd rather hire
a competent but dishonest man?
Eun-tae.
You really worry me sometimes.
Have you ever driven a nice car?
- Pardon? - You know, an expensive, fast car.
I once got to sit in the passenger seat.
Didn't you feel uneasy?
When a bad driver handles a fancy car
it's the passenger who suffers.
Your car is way too fancy.
Watch how you drive it.
- I don't think it looks right. - Really?
The brighter color might work since it's women's wear.
Yes, but the current trend...
But still...
What about the other colors?
- Something brighter. - Brighter?
- Isn't this too bright? - Are you all staying late?
We have some stuff to wrap up.
It must be done before the holiday.
Finish it up and go home.
I'm heading out.
Bye, Mr. Gong.
- Goodbye. - Enjoy the holiday break.
Mr. Gong!
You left this behind.
I gave it to you. Take it home.
No, sir. It's fine.
I want you to have it.
Mr. Gong.
You don't have to do this.
Please, just take the gift.
Okay, then.
I'm really grateful, but...
When Gi-tae made that mistake, his first concern was
if it would cost me a full-time position.
No one cares if a contract worker gets a holiday gift or not
but you left this under my desk.
I'm really grateful, but...
The more you care...
the more I feel like a contract worker.
I should get back to work now.
Enjoy your holiday.
It was a mistake.
A mistake I can't make up, no matter how hard I try.
Today, I ruined a few colleagues' livelihoods.
They might have done wrong
but I was the one to reveal it and get them punished.
My superior criticized me.
The one thing an employee must never hear.
"It's better to be corrupt than incompetent."
That's what he said to me.
VERNIA STUDIO GLOBAL EXPANSION BUSINESS PLAN
I offended a team member in the name of consideration.
I didn't give her the gift for her sake.
I did it for my own.
- That was so good. - I really enjoyed that.
It's a famous place.
It was incredible. Seriously.
Down for another round?
- Let's go somewhere. - For real?
- What should we eat? - What do you want?
Today
as a colleague, a subordinate, and a superior
I accomplished nothing.
I thought things were going well.
I'm rich, so I no longer work to earn a living.
I don't work for the money, so the work became clearer.
I thought everything had changed.
(I can't believe what I'm hearing.)
My circumstances might have improved.
But in reality, nothing has changed.
I was still
a nobody.
I JUST ARRIVED IN BUSAN, MOM
I'M MEETING SOMEONE FIRST SEE YOU LATER
THE X-COORDINATE OF A EQUALS ALPHA...
Multiply both sides by 4x.
Uncle, when did you get here?
A long time ago.
You're joking.
I was watching to see when you'd come.
You're studying here when you don't even study at school?
I study whenever and wherever I can.
- You just don't know me. - You and your nonsense.
- Wait up. - Should we eat something?
Will you buy me what I want?
Name it first. I'll think about it.
I want something expensive.
You said you'd buy me what I wanted.
I didn't say that.
Then why did you even ask?
To eat anything but that.
Jeez, I should order some soju.
Do you want a shot?
You're a horrible uncle.
I used to drink at your age.
These days, only delinquents drink at my age.
I'm only half a delinquent, so I can't drink.
Eat up. Food in Seoul isn't that special, either.
Who eats this these days?
I wanted something from a famous chain.
What's this?
Isn't this a luxury brand?
- You know it? - Of course, I do.
The celebs carry this stuff.
I heard teenagers like it too.
Is it for me?
Uncle, is this how much you care about me?
The food will taste much better now, won't it?
Yeah.
You can't post about it, okay?
I won't. It'll get stolen if I take it to school.
Do you get beaten up and stuff?
I don't.
You need to tell me right away if you do.
I hope you don't get beaten up yourself.
The bus is here.
I'll go ahead.
Get a coffee somewhere and take your time.
What?
You told me to meet you so you could stay out late.
- Well... - Try living with my dad.
You grow up really quickly.
Come home before dinner.
DONGRAE ALTERATIONS
You're here.
Yes, I'm here, Dad.
THE NEW TESTAMENT
Go upstairs. Your mom's waiting for you.
Okay.
Wait.
Your belt buckle's a little loose.
Give it to me.
It looks fine to me.
It's not. Hand it over.
Go up now.
Okay, see you there.
You prepare way too much food.
- We'll never... - I'll pack some for Eun-tae.
We should have plenty for Eun-seok too.
It's too much food, even for that.
Mom, I'm home.
Oh, my gosh. Eun-tae's home.
- Hello, Eun-tae. - How are you?
You should've come home earlier.
My dear boy...
- You look dreadful. - What?
Have you been starving yourself?
I told you to eat on time.
Do you still eat junk food all the time?
Oh, enough with the nagging, Mother.
Give him time to breathe.
Leave it. Berating me gives her joy.
Hello, Uncle.
Long time no see, A-yeong.
You made the long trip to Busan.
Too bad, though.
- The delay was for nothing. - What?
Are you here, Eun-tae?
Why did you come so late?
Didn't you go to work?
No, I heard you'd visit, so I swapped shifts.
Go wash your hands. Let's eat.
Anything good for dinner, Mom?
Let's see.
Oh, you made skewers.
Gosh, it's hot.
You didn't even wash your hands.
So how are things at work?
Why would you ask about work?
Why not? Can't I ask my little brother about his job?
I know you don't care about it. Get to the point.
Can you promise me one thing first?
Don't get annoyed and hear me out first.
Why should I have to promise that? Just talk.
Take a look at this.
It's a door hinge that prevents people from getting hurt.
There's a huge demand for it.
It's going into almost every new apartment.
A surprising number of people get hurt in door hinges.
It looks pretty good.
There's this guy who makes these.
The deals are secured
but he doesn't have the money to keep the factory going.
He says he needs about 100 million won.
I plan to invest.
With what money?
That's why I'm talking to you.
Could you
get me 100 million won?
Eun-seok.
You said some guy made that already.
If he signed deals, there would be sales.
A bank would loan him the money if he had signed contracts.
Getting a loan is like broadcasting he doesn't have the money.
I've known him since I started my own businesses.
He can be trusted, okay?
Even so.
- That's a lot of money. - I know that
you don't have 100 million in cash right now.
Don't you think
you could get a loan somehow?
You want me to take out a loan?
Eun-tae.
I know I got myself into a lot of trouble so far.
- How can you say that? - Hear me out, will you?
- I have a hunch. - Will you stop it?
It's a holiday.
Do you know I stayed out late
just so I could avoid coming home to you?
I did that because I knew you'd be ashamed to see me.
But the first thing you do is ask me for money?
Come on.
How can you do this to me?
Please.
Will you grow up?
I beg of you.
Did you really come late to avoid me?
I didn't know that.
It's just that...
I really thought this was a good idea.
Sorry, man.
Pretend I didn't say a thing.
I'm going downstairs.
Take your time.
THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
ROOF TILE PRAYERS 10,000 PER TILE
My dear son...
MY DEAR SON
May he grow up to be
a decent human being.
GROW UP TO BE A DECENT HUMAN BEING
My dear Eun-tae...
May he meet a good life partner...
MAY HE MEET A GOOD LIFE PARTNER
...and get married one day.
Excuse me, Venerable Sir.
I took a break to stretch and relax.
Does that mean I have to start over?
You can keep going.
Okay, thank you.
MY DEAR SON... MY DEAR EUN-TAE...
MY DEAR SEON-HYUK...
MAY HIS BUSINESS FLOURISH ONE WAY OR ANOTHER
Subtitles by Jennifer Jean Lim